Tufts Review UP065
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Review
1970 -- 1982
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Alumni Relations
UP065
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of the Tufts Review, a semi-annual newsletter sent to donors. Formerly the Tufts Alumni Review. The Tufts Review ceased publication in 1982.
Related Materials
UP004, Tufts Alumni Review, DCA
UP003, Tufts Topics, DCA
UP052, Tufts Magazine, DCA
UP053, Tufts Criterion, DCA
- Tufts Review, 1970 -- 1982; UP065.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of the Tufts Review, a semi-annual newsletter sent to donors. Formerly the Tufts Alumni Review. The Tufts Review ceased publication in 1982.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1970; UP065.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Winter, 1970 -- 1971; UP065.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1975; UP065.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    Issue
    1
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1975; UP065.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    2
  - Tufts Review, Fall, 1975; UP065.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1976; UP065.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1977; UP065.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1978; UP065.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1979; UP065.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1980; UP065.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Winter, 1980; UP065.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1981; UP065.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Review, Spring, 1982; UP065.001.001.00013 (Box 1)